mosw.com 2016-11-05

# San Pedro Software Inc.: Privacy/Security/Delivery/Refund Policy

Privacy Policy \- Security Policy \- Delivery Policy \- Refund Policy

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like San Pedro Software Inc. We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy.

We're based in Belize, our principal activity is software development. Our privacy policy covers San Pedro Software Inc. and its web site:

Organisation Name:| San Pedro Software Inc.  
---|---  
Address:| 7 Craig Street, P.O.Box 322  
City:| Belize City  
Country:| Belize  
Web site:| www.sanpedrosoftware.com  
  
**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

**Cookies**

In respect to Cookies: We use only session Cookies, that is Cookies that are automatically deleted once you close your Internet browser. These cookies do not hold any personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We use Cookies for: proper function of logging into customer's area and keeping our web site functionality during the session, and also to track URLs of sites, from which the visitors come to our site.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. We reserve the right to collect the following personal data for the following purposes:

Purpose| Data collected  
---|---  
billing purposes| full name, card details and/or other financial identifiers, address, phone/fax, email, IP address  
customer support| full name, phone/fax, email, IP address  
  
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated above. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: [info@sanpedrosoftware.com](mailto:info@sanpedrosoftware.com).

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. We make reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection of the child's personal data.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations. 

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an email ([info@sanpedrosoftware.com](mailto:info@sanpedrosoftware.com)), we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week, or we assure you that we hold no personal data about you. Although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified or amended, or completed. We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**SSL 128-bit Encrypted Communication**

Shopping at www.sanpedrosoftware.com is safe. We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details)
  * financial identifiers (such as credit card details)

We have digital certificate issued by Starfield Secure Certification Authority for SSL 128-bit encrypted communication installed on our server (https://www.sanpedrosoftware.com/). This ensures the identity of our server, thus establishing a secure communication between you and our server.

**Security measures**

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

Every software product purchased at our site is accessed by electronic means of delivery. We do not ship the products on CDs, DVDs or any other physical media.

Upon successful purchase, the purchased product can be downloaded instantly from our web site. You can also download the product later at any time by logging into the Customer Support section of our website. If you encounter technical difficulties downloading the purchased product, please contact us at: [info@sanpedrosoftware.com](mailto:info@sanpedrosoftware.com) and we'll respond in 48 hours on business days with solution or another mean of delivery.

Our website features miscellaneous software programs and utilities. You are encouraged to take a close look at all features presented prior to purchasing particular software product, in order to have a good idea about the product capabilities. Once you have purchased the product a technical support team is available for you in the Customer Support section of our website, or at this email address: [info@sanpedrosoftware.com](mailto:info@sanpedrosoftware.com).

We provide 30-day money back guarantee for all our products, provided:

  * Our product has design faults and bugs preventing you to work properly, or
  * Our product does not work as advertised, or
  * You misrepresent vital product features making the purchase worthless to you, or
  * You can provide an objective account of why the product did not work for you

Particular products may come with additional refund policies. These by no means revoke the above refund reasons. NO refund fees are charged.

© 2011 San Pedro Software Inc. All rights reserved.
